Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Basketball Negatives, circa 1926-1991; undated; 2
  - Games, 9
    - Duke's Freshman Team vs. Duke's Varsity Team, 1955 Dec. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01107)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1956 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01108)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1956 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01109)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1957 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01110)
    - Duke vs. Maryland, 1958 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01111)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina, 1958 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01112)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1958 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01113)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1960 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01114)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1960 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01115)
    - Dixie Classics - Various Teams, 1960 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01116)
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph (NCAA, Charlotte, NC), 1960 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01117)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1960 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01118)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01119)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01120)
    - Duke vs. Virginia, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01121)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01122)
    - Duke vs. UNC (Dixie Classics), 1961 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01123)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest (ACC Tournament), 1961 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01124)
    - Duke vs. Clemson [?] (ACC Tournament), 1961-1962 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01125)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01126)
    - Duke vs. Penn State, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01127)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1962 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01128)
    - Duke (Freshman Team) vs. Navy South Atlantic Fleet, 1962 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01129)
    - Duke vs. Maryland, 1962 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01130)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1962 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01131)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1962 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01132)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1963 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01133)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1963 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01134)
    - ACC Tournament - Various Teams, 1963 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01135)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01136)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1967 Feb. 21 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01137)
    - Duke vs. Princeton, 1967 Dec. 19 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01138)
    - Duke vs. Virginia, 1967 Dec. 31 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01139)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 1967 Dec. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01140)
    - Duke (Freshman Team) vs. Davidson, 1968 Jan. 3 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01141)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1968 Jan. 27 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01142)
    - Duke vs. ECU, 1968 Feb. 17 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01143)
    - Duke vs. Temple, 1968 Feb. 17 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01144)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina, 1968 Feb. 24 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01145)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1968 Mar. 2 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01146)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1968 Dec. 20 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01147)
    - Duke vs. Maryland, 1969 Jan. 11 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01148)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina, 1969 Feb. 8 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01149)
    - Duke vs. UNC, circa 1970s (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01150)
    - Duke vs. Maryland, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01151)
    - Duke vs. Davidson, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01152)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01153)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 1971 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01154)
    - Duke (Freshman Team) vs. Davidson, 1971 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01155)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1971 Nov. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01156)
    - Duke (Freshman Team) vs. Virginia, 1971 Dec. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01157)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01158)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1974 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01159)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1974 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01160)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1974 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01161)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian St. Univ., 1974 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01162)
    - Duke vs. LNII Tigers, 1974 Feb. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01163)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1975 Mar. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01164)
    - Duke vs. Johns Hopkins, 1976 Nov. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01165)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1977 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01166)
    - Duke vs. Washington, 1977 Nov. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01167)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1978 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01168)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1978 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01169)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1978 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01170)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1978 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01171)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1978 Jan. (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01172)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1978 Jan. 14 (Box 8, Item UA13020018-N-01173)
    - Duke vs. ECU, 1978 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01174)
    - Duke vs. Virginia, 1978 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01175)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1978 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01176)
    - Duke vs. SMU, 1978 Nov. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01177)
    - Duke vs. LaSalle, 1978 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01178)
    - Duke vs. Loyola, 1983 Jan. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01179)
    - Duke vs. Loyola, 1983 Jan. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01180)
    - Duke vs. South Florida, 1983 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01181)
    - Duke vs. South Florida, 1983 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01182)
    - Duke vs. unidentified, undated (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01183)
  - Miscellaneous, 10
    - Crowd at unidentified game, 1940, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04998)
    - Parker High of Greenville, SC (Runners-Up in the Duke-Durham Basketball Tournament), 1940 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01184)
    - Dedication of Cameron (Luminaries: Wilbur Wade Card, Harry Councillor, Bill Werber, Roland Parley), 1940 Jan. 6 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01185)
    - Dedication of Cameron (Luminaries: Clarence Parker, Bill Werber, Lovell Dean), 1940 Jan. 6 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01186)
    - Dedication of Cameron (Luminaries: Bill Kiker, H. E. Spence, T. G. Stem, Wilbur Wade Card, Paul Kiker [all members of the 1906 team], H. G. Hedrick), 1940 Jan. 6 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01187)
    - Dedication of Cameron (Luminaries: Bill Kiker, H. E. Spence, T. G. Stem, Wilbur Wade Card, Paul Kiker [all members of the 1906 team], 1940 Jan. 6 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01188)
    - Dedication of Cameron (Luminaries: Harry Councillor, Roland Farley, Bill Werber [all members of the 1930 team]), 1940 Jan. 6 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01189)
    - High School Tournament (featuring teams and attendees, including Durham High School), 1940 Mar. 15, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04999)
    - High School Tournament (featuring teams and attendees, including Durham High School), 1940 Mar. 15 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01190)
    - Cameron Indoor Stadium (Interior), 1941 Oct. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01191)
    - Sponsors of the Southern Conference Tournament (unidentified females), 1947 Mar. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01192)
    - Southern Conference Tournament Presentation to Case, NC State, 1949 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01193)
    - Southern Conference Tournament Officials (unidentified), 1949 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01194)
    - Southern Conference Tournament Coaches (unidentified), 1950 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01195)
    - Awards Presentation, 1958 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01196)
    - Crowd at Gym (Cameron, exterior), 1961 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01197)
    - Women's Basketball Clinic Promotion (unidentified male players and staff, unidentified women and girl attendees), 1961 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01198)
    - Practice (Varsity and Freshman teams), 1961 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01199)
    - Clinic Attendees (unidentified), 1963 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01200)
    - Pep Rally (Send Off), 1963 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01201)
    - Hand for ACC Tournament (3 Fingers Up), 1965 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01202)
    - Clinic Attendees (unidentified), 1975 July (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01203)
    - Practice (Opening Day), 1977 Oct. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01204)
    - Cameron Crazies (Duke vs. UNC), 1978 Jan. 14 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01205)
    - Crowd (unidentified Game, copy negative), 1978 Nov. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01206)
    - Posters (color), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01207)
    - Blue Devil Poster (copy negative), 1978 July (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01208)
    - Blue Devil Poster (copy negative), 1978 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01209)
    - Media Guide Cover (copy negative), 1978-1979 season (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01210)
    - Painting of 1977-1978 Team (copy negative), 1979 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01211)
    - Poster Shots (Courtroom Theme), 1981-1982 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01212)
    - Poster Shots (Chemistry Theme), 1985-1986 (6 sleeves) (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01213)
    - Educational Network Playground Poster Shots, circa 1989-1990 (4 sleeves) (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01214)
    - "Duke's Young Guns" (copy negative of team poster), 1990-1991 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01215)
    - Trophy Shot of Final Four Trophies, 1991 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01216)
    - NCAA Basketball Championship Trophy, 1991 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01217)
    - Duke Championship Book Cover, undated (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01218)
- Boxing Negatives, circa 1928-1940; 3
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 11
    - Alterman, Abe, 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05000)
    - Baker, Lenox D. (trainer), 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05001)
    - Baker, Lenox D. (trainer), 1931 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01219)
    - Bolich, Phil, 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05002)
    - Brandon, Dan, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05003)
    - Brewer, Pierce, "Kid" and "Kidd," 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05004)
    - Brooks, Pete (with unidentified wrestler), 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05005)
    - Brooks, Pete, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01220)
    - Brownlee, John, circa 1931-1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05006)
    - Carper, John (with Ned Smith), circa 1928-1929, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05007)
    - Farrar, Danny, 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05008)
    - Farrar, Danny, 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05009)
    - Fraas, George, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05010)
    - Fraser, Lou, 1938 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01221)
    - Fuller, S. Bacon, circa 1929, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05011)
    - Gardner, Joe, 1938 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01222)
    - Goode, Tom, 1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05012)
    - Granger, James "Sully," 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05013)
    - Hyatt, Don, circa 1929, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05014)
    - Jordan, Faison, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01223)
    - Kasik, Chuck, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05015)
    - Kasik, Chuck, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01224)
    - Kirkman, Percy V., 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05016)
    - Kirkman, Percy V., 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01225)
    - Kneipp, Jack, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05017)
    - Koger, Bobby, 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05018)
    - Latimer, Tom, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01226)
    - Lester, Joe, circa 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05019)
    - Little, Robert "Smitty," 1938 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01227)
    - Mann, Alphonso (Al) (alone and with brother Wilton), 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05020)
    - Mann, Wilton, 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05021)
    - Martin, William Southgate "Shack" (alone, with Bill Applewhite, with Emile St. Amand), 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05022)
    - Matulewicz, Ray, 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05023)
    - Matulewicz, Ray (with Coach Addison Warren), 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05024)
    - McCall, Jim, 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05025)
    - Morel, Ed, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01228)
    - Murphy, John, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05026)
    - Parrish, Al, circa 1932-1933, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05027)
    - Price, Robert (Bobby), 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05028)
    - Price, Robert (Bobby), 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05029)
    - Rankin, Cecil Coke, circa 1928-1929, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05030)
    - Ribar, Frank, 1940 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01229)
    - Scelza, Joe, circa 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05031)
    - Schmidt, Don, 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05032)
    - Schmidt, Don, 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05033)
    - Scott, Hoyle "Rip," circa 1929-1933, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05034)
    - Senhauser, Bill, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01230)
    - Sides, Leroy, circa 1931-1933, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05035)
    - Starnes, Ralph, circa 1929-1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05036)
    - Vincent, Orville "Swede," 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05037)
    - Warren, Addison (Coach), 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05038)
    - Warren, Addison (Coach), 1936 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01231)
    - Wentz, Lester, circa 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05039)
    - Winslow, Chuck, circa 1931-1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05040)
  - Teams, 12
    - Team, 1929, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05041)
    - Team, 1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05042)
    - Team, 1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05043)
    - Team, 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05044)
    - Team, 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05045)
    - Team, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05046)
    - Team (Freshman), 1937-1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05047)
    - Team, 1937-1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05048)
    - Team, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01232)
    - Team, 1940 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01233)
  - Games, 13
    - Matches - Action, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05049)
    - Matches - Action, 1939 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01234)
- Cheerleading Negatives, 1939-1990; 4
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 14
    - Durrah, Bobby, 1977 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01235)
    - Ferguson, Lance, 1976 May (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01236)
    - Fetterolf, Katie, 1971 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01237)
    - Howson, George Jr. (Head Cheerleader), 1976 May (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01238)
    - Ulrich, Max, 1976 Apr. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01239)
  - Groups, 15
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified (with crowd at unidentified football game), 1939 Oct. 21 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01240)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified (with band and Duke mascot at unidentified football game), 1941 Oct. 18, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05050)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified (Duke vs. Maryland football game), 1947 Sept. 27, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05051)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified (Duke vs. UNC football game), 1959 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01241)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified, 1973 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01242)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified, 1974 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01243)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified, 1974 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01244)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified (with Duke mascot at unidentified basketball game), 1976 Nov. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01245)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified (Duke vs. Wake Forest game), 1977 Jan. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01246)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified( Duke vs. UNC basketball game), 1978 Jan. 14 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01247)
    - Cheerleaders, unidentified, 1978 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01248)
    - Cheerleaders, Varsity, unidentified (color), 1989-1990 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01249)
- Cross Country Negatives, 1932-1976; 5
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 16
    - Lacy, Phil (with Jack Morse), 1966 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01250)
    - Rogers, Paul Hamilton, circa 1967 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01251)
    - Stenberg, Ed (with Paul Rogers), 1967 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01252)
    - Stenberg, Ed (with Mike Graves), 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01253)
    - Von Klemperer, Will (with Tom Talbott), 1966 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01254)
    - Weisiger, Cary, 1956 Aug. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01255)
    - Weisiger, Cary (with Coach Al Buehler), 1957 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01256)
    - Zodda, Fred (with Bill Weldon), 1966 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01257)
  - Groups, 17
    - Runners, unidentified, 1960 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01258)
    - Runners, unidentified, 1961 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01259)
    - Runners, unidentified, 1967 Oct. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01260)
    - Runners, unidentified, 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01261)
    - Runners, unidentified, 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01262)
    - Roger Beardmore, Phil Wilson, Phil Sparling, Chris Lee, 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01263)
    - Randy Rost, Mark Wellner, Rob Leutwiler, Larry Forrester, 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01264)
    - Runners, unidentified, 1975 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01265)
  - Teams, 18
    - Team, 1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05052)
    - Team, 1933, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05053)
    - Team, 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05054)
    - Team, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05055)
    - Team, 1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05056)
    - Team, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05057)
    - Team, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05058)
    - Team, 1940 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01266)
    - Team, 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05059)
    - Team, 1944 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01267)
    - Team, 1955 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01268)
    - Team, 1956 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01269)
    - Team, 1957 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01270)
    - Team, 1960 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01271)
    - Team, 1961 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01272)
    - Team, 1963 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01273)
    - Team (Freshman team), 1965 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01274)
    - Team, 1965 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01275)
    - Team (identified), 1966 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01276)
    - Team, 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01277)
    - Team (identified), 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01278)
    - Team (identified), 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01279)
    - Team (identified), 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01280)
    - Team, 1974 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01281)
    - Team, 1975 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01282)
  - Games, 19
    - Race: Duke vs. unidentified, 1959 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01283)
    - Race: Duke vs. UNC, 1962 Nov. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01284)
  - Miscellaneous, 20
    - Map, 1964 Oct. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01285)
    - Awards, 1973 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01286)
    - "Iron Dukes in Action," copy negative of a print item, 1976 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01287)
    - "Iron Dukes in Action," copy negative of a print item, 1976 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01288)
- Fencing Negatives, 1965-1985; undated; 6
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 21
    - Bradley, Walt, 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01289)
    - Dybdahl, Ryan, circa 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01290)
    - Kador, John (Coach), 1975 Oct. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01291)
    - Melville, John, circa 1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01292)
    - Moffatt, Tom (with John McFarland), 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01293)
    - Moritz, Al, circa 1967 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01294)
    - Perett, Greg, circa 1965-1967 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01295)
    - Peyser, Jay Randall (Randy), circa 1968, 1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01296)
    - Team Captain, unidentified), 1972 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01297)
    - Team Captain, unidentified), 1973 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01298)
  - Groups, 22
    - Fencers, unidentified, 1965 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01299)
    - Fencers, unidentified, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01300)
  - Teams, 23
    - Fencers, unidentified, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01301)
    - Fencers, unidentified, 1972 Dec. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01302)
    - Fencing Team, 1965 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01303)
    - Fencing Team, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01304)
    - Fencing Team, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01305)
    - Fencing Team, 1978 Feb. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01306)
    - Fencing Team, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01307)
  - Games, 24
    - Dueling Action, 1964 March (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01308)
  - Miscellaneous, 25
    - Fencing Mask, undated (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01309)
- Field Hockey Negatives, 1977-1981; 7
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 26
    - Ennis, Katherine, 1977 Apr. 18 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01310)
    - Silar, Jacki (Coach), 1981 July (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01311)
    - Player, unidentified, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01312)
    - Player, unidentified, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01313)
    - Player, unidentified, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01314)
    - Player, unidentified, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01315)
    - Player, unidentified, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01316)
    - Player, unidentified, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01317)
  - Teams, 27
    - Team, 1978 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01318)
    - Team, 1979 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01319)
    - Team, 1980 Sept. (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01320)
- Football Negatives, circa 1924-1992; 1995; undated; 8
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 28
    - Abbott, Clark, 1955 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01321)
    - Abbott, Ken, circa 1933-1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05060)
    - Abdella, David "Dixie," 1966-1967 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01322)
    - Adams, Charles, 1951 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01323)
    - Adams, Bob, 1965 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01324)
    - Adams, Dan (Freshman team), 1949 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01325)
    - Adams, Rex, 1958 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01326)
    - Addesa, Mike, 1976 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01327)
    - Addesa, Mike, 1977 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01328)
    - Addesa, Mike, 1978 (Box 9, Item UA13020018-N-01329)
    - Addoms, John (Assistant Trainer), 1967 Sept. (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01330)
    - Adkins, Emory "Knocker," circa 1929-1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05061)
    - Alabaster, Bob, 1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05062)
    - Albright, Bob, 1972 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01331)
    - Albright, Bob, 1972 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01332)
    - Albright, Bob, 1973 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01333)
    - Aldridge, Bryant, 1953-1955 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01334)
    - Alexander, Jack, 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05063)
    - Alexander, John Charles, 1966, 1967 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01335)
    - Algor, Jack, 1976 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01336)
    - Algor, Jack, 1977 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01337)
    - Algor, Jack, 1978 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01338)
    - Allen, Lou, 1949 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01339)
    - Alley, Bob, 1933, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05064)
    - Allie, Deems Lee, circa 1958-1959 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01340)
    - Allie, Deems Lee (with Art Browning, co-captains), 1960 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01341)
    - Alston, Bill, 1940, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05065)
    - Altman, Donald, circa 1958-1959 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01342)
    - Alvarez, William J., 1962 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01343)
    - Anderson, Bob, 1949 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01344)
    - Anderson, Everett, 1953 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01345)
    - Anthony, Joseph Peter, Jr., 1959 (Box 10, Item UA13020018-N-01346)